nigelohara.com 2011-01-31

# Nigel O'Hara - Diamond Jeweller - Privacy

Accurist, Citizen, D&G, Guess, Ice Watch, POLICE, Seksy, Seiko, Sekonda, Timex, Tissot , designer watches

We recognize that privacy is important. This Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by nigelohara.com. 

**Information we collect and how we use it:**

In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information: 

  * Information you provide - When you sign up for an Account or promotion that requires registration, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password). For certain services, such as our online purchasing, we also request credit card or other payment account information which we maintain in encrypted form on secure servers. 
  * Cookies - When you visit nigelohara.com, we send one or more cookies - a small file which we use to enchance your browsing experience at nigelohara.com 
  * User communications - When you send email or other communication to nigelohara.com, we may retain those communications in order to process your enquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.
  * We do not store any financial or credit card information on our servers.

nigelohara.com only processes personal information for the purposes described in the applicable Privacy Policy and/or privacy notice for specific services. 

**Information sharing**

We do NOT share your personal information with any other company or persons. 

**Information security**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.
